We did that because people think they're born gay, and I don't think they're born gay.
The amount of left-handed people back in the day was really low.
Because people with left-handed were seen as inferior, and they were forced to use their right hand more often.
But as it became more acceptable, then the amount of left-handed people increased, and it became steady at what, like?
12%.
Would you say people choose to be left-handed?
Uh, I don't know. I don't know anything about it.
Do you choose every day to be attracted to women?
Yes!
No, I wouldn't say so.
Right.
Yeah, I don't think I, I, I'm just naturally attracted to women.
So do I need to connect the dots, or you got it?
No, he's too stupid! He doesn't understand!
Let me think about it. Hold on.
Go ahead.
I can collect my thoughts.
Go ahead, it's all good. Take your time.